favorite-casino.com 2012-10-17

# Favorite Casino - LR - PM - Visa/Master - Privacy Policy

### Privacy policy

This privacy policy sets out how Favorite Casino - LR - PM - Visa/Master uses and protects any information that you give Favorite Casino - LR - PM - Visa/Master when you use this website. Favorite Casino - LR - PM - Visa/Master is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement. 

Favorite Casino - LR - PM - Visa/Master may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes. 

#### What we collect

We may collect the following information:

  * your nickname and your name 
  * contact information including email address 
  * your IP address 

#### What we do with the information we gather

We require this information to understand your needs and provide you with a better service, and in particular for the following reasons: 

  * Internal record keeping. 
  * We may use the information to improve our products and services. 
  * We may periodically send promotional emails about new features, special offers or other information which we think you may find interesting using the email address which you have provided, unless you chose not to receive newsletter during registration 
  * We will send you emails confirming your activities at our website, such as deposits, cashouts 
  * From time to time, unless you chose not to receive newsletter during registration, we may also use your information to contact you by email for market research purposes. 
  * We may use the information to customise the website according to your interests. 

#### Security

We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorised access or disclosure, we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

#### How we use cookies

A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer's hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyse web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences. 

We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyse data about webpage traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We use this information for statistical analysis purposes. 

We also use cookies to keep information about your referer, to pay your referer reward. We also use cookies to keep information about your game preferences (such as Sound on/off, Animation on/off and etc). Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us. 

You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website. 

#### Links to other websites

Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question. 

#### Controlling your personal information

You may choose to restrict the collection or use of your personal information in the following ways: 

  * whenever you are asked to fill in a form on the website, look for the box that you can click to indicate that you do not want the information to be used by anybody for direct marketing purposes 
  * if you have previously agreed to us using your personal information for direct marketing purposes, you may change your mind at any time by logging in at our website, going to Profile page and unchecking “Receive newsletter” checkbox (then click “Continue” button to save changes). 

We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law to do so. We may use your personal information to send you promotional information about third parties which we think you may find interesting if you tell us that you wish this to happen.
